[ "cards":[    {
        "front": "Ordered collection of values",
        "back": "Array"
    },
    {
        "front": "Collection Type",
        "back": "Array"
    },
    {
        "front": "Arrays index start from number",
        "back": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "Array can store what types.",
        "back": "Any, objects and nonobjects"
    },
    {
        "front": "var nameIs: Array<String>",
        "back": "Variable array of strings"
    },
    {
        "front": "var nameIs:  [String]",
        "back": "Variable array of strings"
    },
    {
        "front": "Type inference variable array of strings",
        "back": "var nameIs = [\"to\"]"
    },
    {
        "front": "Adding to a Array.",
        "back": ".append(_;)"
    },
    {
        "front": "Removing and Array item.",
        "back": ".removeAtIndex(_;)"
    },
    {
        "front": "Count of Array items.",
        "back": ".count"
    },
    {
        "front": "Array equality",
        "back": " checked with =="
    },
    {
        "front": "Initializer for variable array empty Integer named test.",
        "back": "var test = [Int]()"
    },
    {
        "front": "Iterate over all array values in array list.",
        "back": "for item in list { }"
    }
    ]
]
